Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Festivals and Delegations
  - Top: A group of tribesmen and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at Sheikh Zayed's majilis. Bottom: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr with a group of military personnel from the court of Sheikh Zayed at his majilis., Circa 1970s; AD_MC_093_ref13_000023_000001; 1 Photogra
    Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Children; Boys; Majilis; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Electricity; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Smoking; Cigarettes; Carpets/Rugs
  - Top: H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki (second from the left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (third from right) in a group of men gathered for a pre-unification conference. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) at a gathering., Circa 1968-1969, 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000024_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Sheikhs; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Unknown Locations; Flags; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Drinks/Beverages
  - The inside back cover of "Festivals and Delegations from the 1960s and early 1970s.", Circa 1960-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000025_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    United Arab Emirates; Qatar; Saudi Arabia; Unknown Locations; London, England, UK
  - The back cover of "Festivals and Delegations from the 1960s and early 1970s.", Circa 1960-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000026_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.5 x 29.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Docks/Piers/Jetties; United Arab Emirates; Saudi Arabia; London, England, UK; Qatar; Unknown Locations
- H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969
  - The front cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969.", AD_MC_093_ref14_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.3 x 38.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Arabic Calligraphy; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Medals/Insignia
  - The inside front cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969.", AD_MC_093_ref14_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Kuwait City, Kuwait
  - A blank page in the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969.", AD_MC_093_ref14_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Facial Hair; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Cameras; Gatherings
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting an unidentified man., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Gatherings
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah receiving gifts from two Kuwaiti school girls., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Girls; Children; Airports; Airplanes; Transportation; Ceremonies; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Gatherings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Arabic Writing; Cameras; Sheikhs; Royalty; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah at the reception of the UAE delegation, with H.E. Khalfan Al Romaithi and the Abu Dhabi delegation in the background., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Ceremonies; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Hats; Officials
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah walking by the Kuwaiti military at the Kuwait International Airport, including H.E. Khulfan Romaithi behind Sheikh Zayed., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Airports; Ceremonies; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Flags; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting the Kuwaiti delegation, with Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah on the right., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Ceremonies; Cameras; Kuwait City, Kuwait
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting the Kuwaiti delegation, with Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah on the right., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Ceremonies; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A group portrait of members of the UAE delegation including H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (middle), H.E. Butti Bin Bishr speaking to three men, and H.E. Sheikh Saeed Bin Hamed Al Nahyan (right)., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Sheikhs; Ceremonies; Kuwait City, Kuwait
  - H.E. Khalifa Bin Yousef Al Suwaidi (far left) and a group of men from the Kuwaiti delegation., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Gatherings; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Kuwait City, Kuwait
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan talking with members of the Kuwaiti delegation in a tent, with H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi and H.E. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Khalid Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on the left., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tents; Carpets/Rugs; Group Portraits; Men; Presidents; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Officials
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a tour, with H.E. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Khalid Bin Sultan Al Nayhan, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, and H.E. Khalfan Al Romaithi behind him., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan sitting on a couch with Jaber Al Ahmad Al Sabah., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Flower Garlands/Bouquets
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting members of the Kuwaiti delegation with Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Officials; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Gatherings
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah walking with members of the Kuwaiti delegation, including H.E. Khalfan Al Romaithi (left of Sheikh Zayed) and Nawaf Al Ahmad Al Jaber Al Sabah (middle, second row) in the background., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials
  - A Kuwaiti man giving H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan a tour of a factory., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Presidents; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Clocks/Watches; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Factories; Medals/Insignia; Officials
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah on a factory tour with members of the UAE delegation, with Nawaf Al Ahmad Al Jaber Al Sabah in the background., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Factories; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Crowds
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with members of the Kuwaiti delegation at the Kuwaiti International Airport., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Furnishings; Gatherings; Ceremonies; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Sheikhs; Officials; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Airports
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah in the foreground, with Jaber Al Ahmed Al Sabah and Nawaf Al Ahmad Al Jaber Al Sabah behind them., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Signs/Signposts; Arabic Writing; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Ceremonies
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a factory tour., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Factories; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Sheikhs; Presidents; Officials; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan
  - H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi with members of the Kuwaiti delegation., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Carpets/Rugs; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Furnishings; Cigarettes; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials
  - A blank page in the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969.", AD_MC_093_ref14_000024_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - The inside back cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969.", AD_MC_093_ref14_000025_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - The back cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969.", AD_MC_093_ref14_000026_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
- H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Al Ain in the 1970s
  - The front cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Al Ain in the 1970s.", Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.5 x 29.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Al Ain, United Arab Emirates
  - The inside front cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Al Ain in the 1970s.", Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.8 x 23.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - A page with Arabic writing in the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Al Ain in the 1970s.", Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.8 x 23.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Arabic Writing; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates
  - A blank page in the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Al Ain in the 1970s.", Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.8 x 23.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr hugging H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Clocks/Watches
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr holding hands with H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Mohamed bin Zayed Scholars Program; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr with H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on their visit to Al Ain., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Military/Soldiers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr viewing a document with Sheikh Khalid Bin Saqer Al Qassimi., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) with three members of H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's court., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Carpets/Rugs; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Officials; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr with a group of performers at an Al Ayala dance., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Dancing; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Guns; Weapons; Tents; Officials; Facial Hair
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (eighth from the left) and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (right) at an Al Ayala dance., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Camels; Animals; Guns; Weapons; Dancing
  - From the left, front row: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Tahnoun bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr touring a construction site with Abd Al Rahman Makhlouf in the background (wearing sunglasses and a tie)., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Construction; Facial Hair
  - From the left, front row: Abd Al Rahman Makhlouf, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr touring a construction site with a group of men in the background., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Sheikhs; Officials; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Construction; Crowds
  - From the left, front row: Abd Al Rahman Makhlouf, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr touring a construction site with a group of men in the background., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Sheikhs; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Crowds
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Tahnoun bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, Abd Al Rahman Makhlouf, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr reviewing plans at a construction site., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials; Presidents; Royalty
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Tahnoun bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, Abd Al Rahman Makhlouf, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr reviewing plans at a construction site., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates
  - From the left, front row: Abd Al Rahman Makhlouf, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr touring a construction site with a group of men in the background., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Construction; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Officials; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Crowds; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms
  - H.E Butti Bin Bishr (middle) with two unidentified men at a meeting regarding the unification of the United Arab Emirates., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Gatherings; Politics; Government
  - H.H. Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at a meeting regarding the unification of the United Arab Emirates., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Officials; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Politics; Government; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings
  - H.H. Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at a meeting regarding the unification of the United Arab Emirates., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Sheikhs; Politics; Government; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair
  - H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at a dinner., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Gatherings; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (standing) at a dinner with other officials., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Gatherings; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Food; Furnishings
  - The inside back cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Al Ain in the 1970s.", Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.8 x 23.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - The back cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Al Ain in the 1970s.", Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref15_000024_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.8 x 23.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
- Al Ayala Dance Perfomance